[music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
All right, y'all. We
are live on this beautiful Sunday
afternoon. God bless everybody in the
name of Yeshua, Jesus, the Messiah. I
pray you and your family are super
blessed
as uh man, Bitcoin is about to make a
move and we are trading it live, baby.
We are live right now from the trade
given in the moment
in the New York VIP stream. We are
currently up and we're we're up right
now what
11 grand. We'll call it 11 grand. 11 and
some change. [music] All right. Things
are looking strange, but we're up 11 and
some change.
All right, big shout out to everybody in
the chat, you know. Shout out to Aditi
Haria. How long did it take me to master
market cipher, man? I'm still mastering
it. It's an ongoing thing. You know what
I'm saying? It's a never- ending battle.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, shout out to Vera 4234. BTC2
the moon. Too real for you says explode
up or down. Well, here's the thing. Look
for the for the for the clips in the
future, the I told you so clips. Let me
be very clear. Bitcoin is 100% going to
explode to the upside this week.
Clip that. All right.
Bitcoin is 100% going to explode to the
downside this week.
Clip both of those, guys. And uh
whichever one happens this week, I will
gladly say I was right and I predicted
it and all that good stuff. So make sure
to subscribe to the channel and make
sure to sign up to my paid group cuz I
predicted exactly what was going to
happen with Bitcoin. [music]
Um
I don't know honestly. I have no idea
guys. This is some low volatility stuff.
But but here's the one thing I do know
for certain. There is going to be a big
move very soon. The reason is because we
are consolidating very very tightly at a
very key level, the 65.6 $67,000 level.
And if we cannot blast through here and
if we do reclaim it, we are going to get
a significant follow through to the
upside. But if we reject, we're going to
come back down probably to the bottom of
the range. So, you can only squeeze so
long before something happens.
All right? I mean, that's just that's
just the reality of life, guys. You can
only squeeze so long until something
happens.
You know what I mean?
I mean, I'm I'm picturing anything in
life. An an orange, take an orange. You
only squeeze the orange so long until
something happens. All right? Either the
orange gives out or your hand cramps up,
you know? Either the orange gives out or
or or or your hand cramps up, you know.
Big shout out to
Larry Garcia. What's going on my man
Larry Garcia? Shout out to Sea Train
2323. Shout out to 20 Yeshu from India.
God bless you. Shout out to Krypto
Scarface 618 and Kipcorn Sheriff. New
week, new chances. New week, new
channel. Big shout out to my man Evan
Aldo,
bro. Good to see you, man. God bless
you, bro. It's good to see you here. He
says, "What's up, Jason Casper? I think
we break upward next week. I hope we do.
Evan Aldo, I've been I've been kind of
more bullish than bearish lately, but
you know, the longer we consolidate
here, the more it's like I I just don't
know. I just don't know. You know, I
hope I hope these high time frame
divergences play out, man. The weekly,
the two-weekly has confirmed as well.
Um, yeah, things are looking like we
could get the move up to
at least at least 67 68, but Maybe the
maybe the mid70s, man. The value area
high of this local ranger. Actually,
Evan Aldo, bro, I just I literally just
commented on one of your Twitter posts.
I just commented on one of Evan Aldo's
Twitter posts, guys. Go follow Evan
Aldo.
Evan Aldo on Twitter. He asked this
question. What when did he ask the
question? It must have been a while ago.
Yeah, here we go. He asked it two days
ago. If someone gives you $10 million to
invest in anything except index funds,
how do you invest it? That's a good
question.
Oh, look. He He saw it, man. That's
probably why he's on the stream right
now. Yeah, I I You know what? I'm going
to ignore I'm going to ignore the second
half of the sentence here. My answer was
if someone gives me $10 million, I will
simply just long the exact top 100x
leverage, billion dollar position size.
Evan Aldo says probably the best
investment.
All right, he says probably the best
investment. That's exactly word for word
what Evan Aldo said here. All right,
let's
What the heck? Our screen just went
black. Our screen just went black.
Hm. How do I fix this?
Probably the best investment a person
could make. Honestly,
big shout out to Evan Aldno. Yes,
explosion time. You can see that I'm
open-minded. Look, I try to remain
open-minded about the charts. Big shout
out to Fatasum Fatal Sumo. What's going
on, bro? Um, explosion time. Absolutely.
Absolutely. Handyman Services says,
"Happy Sunday, Jay. Happy Sunday to you
as well." Shout out Shout out to uh Matt
Yarkadi
2171. Hey Jay, can you explain from day
one of someone trading until he becomes
profitable? What are the things he has
to do? Well, he has to learn technical
analysis. That's the first thing. Then
he has to have some kind of strategy
that's based on the analysis that tells
him when to take a trade and when not to
take a trade. And then after that, all
right, after that
he needs to master risk management. Then
after that, he needs to master
the discipline and the psychology to
stick to the risk management and the
strategy. And then after that, he's
going to have to go through a few
winning streaks and feel like the best
trader in the world and go through a few
losing streaks and feel like an absolute
idiot. Then he's going to have to learn
how to trade different market
conditions.
And he's going to have to learn when to
not trade and when to trade.
And and then I think you you'll probably
be there, man. Honestly,
you have to go through those things. In
my experience, I I feel like everyone
has to go through them.
Uh hopefully you don't go through losing
a lot of money though. That's a big
thing that a lot of people go through
that is not necessary to go through. But
the problem is a lot of people well you
know it's it's very difficult to be
disciplined and all that and you end up
like you could blow like a month's worth
of good trading in a day if you're just
sitting there revenge trading all day
long. It's it's it's a terrible thing.
How many hours of back test? I don't
know, man. I honestly don't know.
Do I still do giveaways? Of course I do.
In fact, how many people we got in here?
300. Wow. I finally made it. I finally
made it. Let's see. Can we smash the
likes up to the watchers? Maybe I'll
give away $500 right now. I mean, who
the heck cares? It's only $500. Shout
out to Crypto Scarface. He says,
"Bitcoin is consolidating inside the
local supply zone. If it breaks above
with acceptance, next target 67K."
Absolutely 67K. Thank you so much,
Krypto Scarface, for that beautiful
super chat. Whoa.
Oh, man. Thank you so much for that
beautiful super chat there,
man. What is going on with this? Yeah.
So, I agree with you. 67K is the next
spot. I'd say we're probably going to
overshoot 67K a little bit just to like
get people ultra bullish. But if we can
flip 67K into support, then uh yeah, for
sure we could get up a little bit
higher. and we're going to be diving
into the charts. We are coming into a
new week here. We are coming straight
into actually technically it is a new
week. All right. [music] Shout out to
Dave Flowers. I love you, bro. And may
God bless you and your loved ones in
Jesus name. Uh he has to get liquidated
for 3 years. Hopefully not, man.
Hopefully not. Hopefully not.
Shout out to Deathwish Gaming YouTube.
What's going on, man? Um, weekly unbutt
cheeks never fails. Yeah, spiky TV. See,
here's the thing. We are in a strange
situation right now. We are in a very
strange situation right now because the
last [music] time we printed the weekly
uneven butt cheek pattern, it was the
exact bottom of the bare market. And
guess what? Before this time, it had
never happened before. This is uncharted
territory in a sense that it hasn't even
been a year since the all-time high. And
we're printing a historic bottom signal
that's only printed once in the past
before. So yes, the green box and the
green line is the projected target for
the bottom of this bare market. Could
the bottom be in here? The answer is
yes, it could be based on this based on
this bullish divergence. It could be.
Would I like the bottom to be in now?
The answer is no. I wouldn't. I would
prefer this uneven butt cheek to give us
a bit of a bull trap. I would like maybe
for us to stay in this range for a
little bit longer, then get a big fake
out to the downside, come back inside
the range, and then blast. That's what I
would like. I would like some kind of
capitulation, big bottom. But we might
not get that cuz what we did, we didn't
have any kind of big major top, right?
It was it was a very a very antilimactic
bull market, so to speak. Evan Aldo, he
says, "Discipline is life." That is so
true, guys. And here's here's here's a
little pro tip. All right. If you can
discipline yourself in one area of life,
it will transfer over to other areas of
your life. That's 100% true. If you can
be disciplined in certain areas of your
life, it will transfer over to other
areas. If you can discipline yourself
spiritually, if you can discipline
yourself physically,
it will help you discipline yourself
mentally, [music]
psychologically, especially as it
pertains to trading the charts, right?
When you can get into the habit of
depriving yourself of instant
gratifications and doing things that you
don't really want to do, but you do them
anyway because you're disciplined, that
will spill over into other areas of your
life.
Big shout out to Divine Hood. God bless
you, bro. I'm having an excellent
weekend, my friend. [music] You know, my
first weekend of being 36 after being
35. And I do have to say, you know what?
I feel like puberty finally kicked in
cuz the beard
is is thicker than ever before, man.
It is thicker than ever before. Let me
tell you, pretty soon I'm be looking
like Trader Gio. All right.
Discipline is freedom. That is 100% the
truth as well. Discipline is freedom.
Yeah. Uh it's it's so interesting
because you know as I
as I have gone through life, trying as
hard as I can to be as lazy as possible,
uh you know, like trying not to have a
job, [music] all these types of things.
It just means you have to do more work.
And it also means you have to be much
more disciplined cuz if you don't have a
job,
you're the only one [laughter]
you're the only one there to do the
work. And if you don't do it, I mean,
that's it. So, yeah, discipline equals
freedom. You can be disciplined in all
those different areas of your life. Life
is going to be easier. What What do they
say? They say hard decisions now, easy
life later. Easy decisions now, hard
life later. There's a lot of truth to
that. Obviously, everybody is dealt a
different hand in life, right? So, it
it's a general principle. Obviously,
it's not going to look the same for
every person, right? But it is
definitely a true general principle.
Um, shout out to Ma Kodak from Iran. God
bless you, bro.
Um, yo, Jason, I just got here and
adding another like to your collection.
Thank you, man. $5,000 giveaway if you'd
like the stream. I said a $500 giveaway
if you like the stream, but you know
what I mean? Maybe I'll maybe I'll do a
$1,000. I I don't know, man. Like,
anything's possible. Anything's
possible. Smash up the dang likes, guys.
We're only one one quarter of the people
liked right now. Uh, shout out to Crypto
for Columbus. What's going on, man? Uh,
yeah, we might as well do a Sunday
giveaway. Jason Casper 3D trigger wave
with the money flow coming up, bro. Pump
it. Why don't I trade forex and gold?
I've traded gold in the past. I'm just a
crypto guy through and through.
set capitulation that you were hoping
for would bring us into next year maybe,
but I wouldn't be so sure, says Damen
Wins. [music] Well, I'm hoping it
happens by the fall. And if it doesn't
happen by the fall, then I'll say, you
know what? I guess the bottom's in. You
know, I guess the bottom's in. Do I
still think we go to 41K? Well,
yeah, I think it's possible. Like,
that's the thing. I think it's possible.
And I'm going to keep giving that target
until until it's January and we haven't
hit that level. You know,
I watch Spider-Man.
There's new Spider-Man. Now, I don't
really watch TV cuz I'm a loser, guys.
I'm a loser. I don't watch TV. I I'm I'm
such a loser. If you guys were to meet
me in real life, you would say, "Man,
Jason Casper, what a loser. What a nerdy
loser. He doesn't do anything funny. His
life is so boring."
That's what you would say if you met
Jason Casper in real life. Okay.
So,
um, Joo said that. Well, you know what?
My nickname is Jaco. I'm not even
kidding with you. What's the best crypto
firm to trade with? Well, you know, I
got to tell you, client funding, cuz I'm
partnered with client funding, but they
are legit and I have 15% discounts on
all these accounts. I'm also affiliated
with Bitfunded. These two crypto prop
firms in my opinion are are the are the
ones to go to. But obviously there's
also Breakout. Breakout's a great cryp
crypto prop firm as well. Breakout's
great too.
Those three. Those three. All right.
Um, [music]
you watch my stream every day. Get to
learn a lot. Oh, that's cool, man. God
bless you, bro. Um, you don't watch TV
either, John KJV. Well, I guess you're a
loser just like me, man. That's cool.
You know what? Losers unite.
What if you take a low leverage short
from her?
Well, I I guess it depends, honestly. Do
you really want to do you really want to
take a loan out from her?
I mean, she might do you dirty.
Honestly, if you're going to borrow
money from her to to take a leverage
trade
from her,
[music] she might really do you dirty,
man. I I would I wouldn't do that. I
wouldn't do that. I would go to the bank
and get a loan. You know, I wouldn't
trust her.
I would not trust her.
But if you're talking about a
lowleverage short trade from here, well,
here's the thing. I don't think the
leverage from here really matters
because
um you know what I would say a low
leverage trade from here is not the best
idea. I would rather take a massively
high leverage trade from here. And I'll
tell you why. Because really, if we're
going to reclaim this level here,
we're going up much higher, right? This
is the top of the local range.
I guess you do need some low leverage
for that. That actually, yeah, now that
now that you mention it, that is I would
just be careful. I Yeah, you're going to
need some leverage for that. Um, but
here's the thing. I would be really
careful about getting into a short trade
from here specifically, [music] just
because again, unless you're hedging
against a long that you already have
open, you're really going to
You know, it's like you got to cut that
thing after 5%. You'd have to have such
a tiny position size on that. You might
as well wait for a better setup that
happens like later in [music] the week.
You know, I have this very itchy bug
bite on my shoulder. I've had it since
last week. Going to use this rubber
chicken to scratch it. This rubber
chicken is textured in such a way that
it really does feel good on the on the
bug bites. You know, I was out the other
day. These these mosquitoes, they ripped
me to shreds, man.
They've ripped me to shreds. Um,
all right. John J.H316
is investing in Bitcoin at 54 years old.
That's what's up, man. You know, I look,
I do think Bitcoin I do think Bitcoin's
a good asset to invest in and right now
think it's a good time to invest because
we're at a 50% discount. If we dump
lower, it's only at a better discount.
If time is money, then TV is way too
expensive. That's how I feel, you know,
whenever I try and do something like
that. I I can only take small doses.
Small doses because then something
inside of me says, [music] "What a wa
why are you wasting your life?" Like
these small doses. I I just can't I
can't take it. I can't take it. I I wish
I could. I wish I honestly I'm not even
kidding you. I wish I was like a normal
guy who like got excited to like come
home from work, crack open a cold beer
and watch sports ball on TV with my
friends and yell at the TV with my beer
belly jiggling all around eating pizza
and just thoroughly enjoying life. I I
know so many guys like that and they
they enjoy life more than I do. They
enjoy life way more than I do. All
right? You know,
but I unfortunately or fortunately,
depending on how you look at it, I just
can't do that. I cannot do that. I
remember when I was in my 20s, I had
friends.
They would get together
to eat pizza, drink beer, and play
cards.
They would do this for hours, multiple
times a week. And I just I mean even
just looking at them made me sick to my
stomach. You disgusting lazy fat. How
could you? But look, I wish I was them.
I wish I wish I could just get enjoyment
from that boring lifewasting stuff, but
I just can't. We got to give a big shout
out to Mikey. Mike, he says, "Jay, can
you please share the playlist you shared
last stream where the Fibonacci I think
it was this one, man?" Yeah, I'll I'll
pop it in the chat. All right. I think
it was this one.
>> I think it was this one here.
>> Let's start this one over.
All right. Big shout out to Mikey Mike
for the super chat. I hesitate to take
the long.
How do you deal with regret? There's
nothing you can do about the regret.
There's nothing you can do. You have to
get over it. It really sucks. Embrace
the suck. Embrace the suck. Embrace it
and you will get over it. All right.
Embrace it and you'll get over it. Is
Bitcoin going up?
S [snorts]
Insights.
I'm 50/50 right now. I am 100% 50/50,
but I'm long and I'm hoping for upside.
But I don't know cuz we are at
resistance here. But I'm I'm about to go
through my actual analysis. I haven't
looked at the chart since Thursday. The
are they the Bill Gates mosquitoes? They
might be, man. Honestly, [music] they
might be. Um, shout out to New Earth
Guardian who says, "Yo, we're rejecting
from the 4hour order uh sell block."
[music]
Yeah, let's Yeah, let's dive into the
chart. Guys, smash up the likes. Let's
see if we can um
we can't get a little bit of a
a little bit of like action here. Maybe
we'll do a giveaway. You can't watch TV
by yourself, but if your wife or
daughter watching, you'll join. Yeah.
Yeah. That's the same with me. Like it's
it's mostly if I'm going to do it, it's
with my kids. But I can only take small
doses. I can only take small doses, you
[music] know?
Especially sitting and watching. Sitting
and watching is the worst. I mean, maybe
if I could be on a treadmill, you know,
at least then I'm like keeping my body
moving or whatever.
Uh use the plunger. Yeah, use the
plunger.
Uh,
if you don't take some time to enjoy the
results of your hard work and
discipline, what's the point? See, yeah,
that's why that's the thing about me. I
can't those things are not enjoyable for
me. So, like that's what makes me so
such a weird That's what makes me such a
loser. Like when I said Jason Casper's
if you hung out with me in real life,
like I'm I'm a loser. Like the things I
enjoy are actually the things that I
just do in general. like I I enjoy
waking up early and and and hitting the
gym and and and studying the Bible and
all the stuff that I do. I actually like
I like that stuff. I don't know. It's
like
I don't know. I don't know what else to
say. That's why I'm such a loser, you
know.
All right, let's pop into the dang
charts, man.
All right, let's let's pop to the dang
charts, man. All right, [music] so let's
pop to the dang charts, man. You know,
let's pop into the dang chart. We're
going to start on the monthly time frame
here.
We understand that what's happening
right now is we are potentially uh about
to print our It's the very beginning of
August. We got three weeks left. If we
get a blue candle, it's nothing too
crazy.
considering this extremely bearish
engulfing candle that we had here from
the month of June, right? Nothing too
crazy yet on the monthly. We did have
two blues back here before the May
candle topped out.
Um, but once we do confirm a green dot,
I would say it's pretty safe to say that
the bottom is actually in two week. What
do we have on the twoe? Confirmed
bullish divergence. Again, the last time
we had this on the two week, the bottom
was already in. the bottom was already
in. Something else that's very
interesting about the confirmed bullish
divergence on the two week last time is
that it happened on a purple candle.
It happened on a purple candle and it
didn't look too bullish honestly. Like
if you had asked anybody back then, how
do you feel about this candle?
You know, how do you feel about the
candle? Let's start new.
You know, how do you feel about this
candle in the moment there? You know,
probably most people say that's not the
most bullish looking candle in the
world, right? We had a big massive
bearish engulfing candle. We had a nice
bullish looking hammer candle, but then
we have a shooting star and we're in the
middle of a bare market, right? Not the
most bullish looking candle, but that
just so happened to be the bottom and
the confirmed bullish divergence on the
twoe gave us the tip off before anything
happened. Like we came, we rejected
literally from the support resistance
flip from the previous range, but then
we just pumped right through it like a
wild lady running through the desert
with a laundry basket on her head the
following [music]
twoe candle. And so it's a very similar
looking candle that we had here. I mean,
look at this here, right? I just want to
say it's very similar looking because we
had the confirmation of the green dot
and we came up and we back tested
basically this support resistance flip,
right? This was our support since
February based on the candle closes. We
come up and we reject from that level.
So it's very very similar. [music] And
now our second twoe candle which has a
week left. Very interesting to see
what's going to happen here. Are we
actually going to get a change of
structure locally? It's very possible
the weekly.
This is where things get even more
interesting because again we have a a
double bottom Bit Boy green dot followed
by a very intense divergence to the
downside bouncing from none other than
the macro Fibonacci golden pocket pull
from the low to the high. Right? So from
the low to the high. We'll take this off
log. We'll put it on linear cuz that's
how I measure this here. We're bouncing
literally from that 618.
So this is a this is a very important
level that we are currently bouncing
from. And also, it's a pretty key level
because if we just, you know, without
any like fancy technical analysis tools
here, we just mark off the previous
cycle all-time highs. Whoops. Let me put
this box back on. Turn off this white
line. We we mark off the previous range
all-time highs. I mean, it was
resistance once, resistance twice,
consolidation, breakout, and now you
could say we're getting a back test with
a double bottom, right? Back test number
one in February. Then we come down, we
get a lower low with a bullish
divergence and maybe this turns into an
accumulation range and we we get
ourselves out of here, right? So far,
you could make a pretty nice case for
that. [music]
Then we come down to our daily time
frame. This is where things get even
more interesting
because not only did we come down to the
golden pocket, the 618 at 50 57.6 6 with
a nice bullish divergence here, but now
we've had a money flow cross on the
daily with a confirmed trigger wave.
Now, here's the thing that concerns me a
little bit. Usually, you get a a signal
like this and it gives you a very strong
reaction so far. I mean, it's been that
was Tuesday. So, Wednesday, Thursday,
Friday, Saturday, it's been 5 days
without like a serious reaction. [music]
You know, when you see really bullish
signals with slow reactions, a lot of
times that means we end up rolling over.
>> [music]
>> So, all that being said, because these
high time frames are super bullish and
even our 4hour time frame as we come
down here, man, like
we obviously have some nice bullish
divergences here, right? We have some
really nice bullish divergences down
here.
Extremely nice looking bull dives here
on the 4hour time frame as we made this
higher [music] low from the bottom,
right? But I really don't like this.
Like this right here does not look nice
to me at all. This looks extremely
squeezable. It looks like if we start to
lose this lower trend line that we could
come all the way back down to the
$60,000 zone, which is going to be the
618786 area right here. like if we start
to lose that, I I would be pretty
positive that we would come down and
take that liquidity cuz we gave it a
really good shot here and then we have
this slow painful grind to the upside.
It just looks like very squeezable. And
it just makes so much sense too that we
would come down to that level because
not only is that the golden pocket,
[music] it's the value area low of the
range. And so you could see right here,
we're grinding up against this
resistance. If we do reject from it,
especially we start to lose this trend
line, it could be a smooth move to the
downside. But on the other side of that
Bitcoin, this consolidation, if it
breaks to the upside, which it very well
may, then I'd say obviously our first
target is the top of this range here.
Our top the top of this range is going
to be I'm going to call it $68,000 cuz
I'm going to take it from these highs
that we made here in on June 2nd.
But if we flip 68K into support, then we
are we are going to come up much higher
and and these these bullish divergences
on the weekly and daily have a lot more
juice in them if the market structure uh
flips bullish here. And when I say the
market structure flips bullish, I'm
really talking about this here, guys.
All right, [music] this is the market
structure I'm talking about. This is the
key support right here, the key
resistance. If we do this [music]
right, we we get that back test where we
we break out and then we hold, you know,
that right there in my opinion is going
to probably give us that big move up to
the top of the range, which is the value
area high of going all the way back to
February, right? Let's go ahead and pull
our volume here. Going all the way back
to February. February.
Yeah, that's going to be insane. That's
going to be insane. That's going to be
insane. We're going to back test the
local range value area high. We really
don't have any resistance until we're
back up to around 74. We pulled the fib
high to low
and yep, this is this is what we're
looking at, guys. Right. This is what
we're looking at here. So, it's very it
going to be very interesting to see what
happens in the next week because
obviously we can see that we are we are
coiling up for a big move. The move to
the downside could be extremely violent
and fast given this disgusting liquidity
that we've been building up in this
little area. The move up to 74 could be
very violent and fast given the fact
that number one, a lot of people are
still very bearish. Number two, there's
no resistance here. We had a very smooth
blue down. We had a very smooth move
down.
All right. Um
but yeah, shout out to the treadmill
walkers. [music]
I see us getting the liquidity and
dropping. That could be nice. And
honestly, if we do grab the liquidity
and drop down, you know, I would still
be very interested
in a long trade from $60,000 cuz I do
think that's a very key support.
Um, and you know, obviously I'm I'm also
looking for a short trade from the top
of the range here, right? We come up
here. If we have some bearish signs,
this is a place that I am absolutely
looking to short, right? Because it is
simply the top of the range. So, even if
we get a fake out up here and then we're
start close below. Yeah, I'm going to be
looking for shorts coming back down at
least to here,
maybe lower. There's so many different
ways you could look at this right now.
You could look at this what I've just
drawn out as [music]
doing this, right? That you have your
shoulder, your head, your shoulder.
Because of the bullishness of the two
week and the weekly and the daily,
you could say, especially after coming
up and making a higher high, that this
is a back test of major support. and
then and then we could take it up to 73.
The other side of that you could say
this was a failed attempt to change
market structure in which case the range
now is going to break down similarly to
how this range broke down and we are
we're going to see lower. Those are
really the two ways to look at it. So
because like there are many different
ways to look at it. You guys know the
way I trade. I trade where I look for a
setup. I take a trade. If the setup
presents itself, I lock in a profit and
then I let I let a runner run. That's
how I do it. I don't try to force the
trades. I don't try to predict anything.
I just wait for price to do its thing
and if I see a setup, if I see we come
up here and instead of getting the back
test, we're falling down below. I have
myself a beautiful short entry. Of
course, I'm going to be looking for this
on the low time frame. You know, if I'm
taking the trade, I'm going to let my
the Casper crew VIP Discord know, you
know, like I do. Look at that. Donald
Trump. Wow. You know, we give the setups
in advance. You know, I tell people when
I'm taking the trade, this trade here
took it live during the New York open
stream, right? We're up 11.5K right now
on one position, baby. Isn't that crazy?
That is crazy. What do I think of all
that remains? Um, well,
you know what? You're talking about the
band. I say I really really really think
that uh it was it was a really good
band. Um you know back in the day when
they were heavier that the album that
had six on it. I forget the name of the
album but then they came out with the
album where they sang a lot more and
they had like way cooler guitar solos. I
thought that was really good too. But I
have to say, sadly, their guitar player
got murdered.
And then, you know, one of the coolest
things I ever witnessed was watching
Jason Richardson fill in for All That
Remains and nail those solos so
perfectly live. What a cool thing.
Um,
incline for max effect on the treadmill.
Yeah, but you got to be careful. You got
to be careful. Nope. Haven't closed the
short, guys. Short is still wide open.
Short is still wide open, baby. So,
you know, I've already I've already told
you guys here, I'm keeping the short
open till the death. It's a zerorisk
trade for me right now. I've locked in a
$4,000 profit. Oh, I'm I'm lo I just got
logged out of the dang exchange here.
Let me see if I can't try this again.
Refresh a little bit here.
Oh, okay. No, we're we're in. It's just
glitched out somehow. I hope [music] so.
Yeah, we're still open. The trades are
still open. I don't know what the heck
is going on here. I probably have to log
out and lock back in. Anyway, yeah, I'm
closing out the trade. It's already at 4
grand. It's going to be a zero loss
trade if it gets stopped out, you know.
Right now, altogether, I think I have
almost a $500,000 position on this long
trade. And then I have like a4 million.
So, I'm at like $750,000 in longs right
now. So, yeah, for me, the short is
worth to have open. More worth now. Um
uh
I like the triple bottom bitcoin form
says too for you. Can we look at Zcash?
We could probably Yeah, we could take a
look at Zcash um for sure.
Uh, let's check out order flow real
quick though because I do want to see
how how the order flow is looking. Um,
how many years of experience do I have
with trading? Well, I've been I've been
trading and investing in some way for 10
years.
And in those 10 years, obviously, my
journey has taken many twists and turns.
But 2016, ah,
the first time I ever purchased anything
to invest in it was 2014.
First time I ever uh started really
buying and selling things to make money
was in 2016.
When did I start actually doing leverage
trading? That was in 2018.
Um,
so I I consider myself doing this
specific thing that I'm doing now for
about eight years.
Let's check out the order flow.
Oo.
Oo anos.
Wow. Okay. So this is the order flow
right now. And what's really standing
out to me is how many positions have
opened up in this move to the upside.
It's very interesting. Wow. So, we had
about 177 million longs on a 500 million
volume candle
and this entire time an increase of open
interest. We're actually seeing
it's very interesting. I I I actually
don't really know. I don't see I don't
see bearish divergences.
I there actually is some maybe some very
slight bearish divergence here.
Is there some slight bullish I mean you
might you could even say that there
maybe is some slight bullish diver. But
anyway, there are people loading up on
trades here and there are they're
they're pretty evenly spread longs and
shorts. So, it's very interesting
because people are putting their money
in the market right now expecting a big
move. They're trying to frontr run the
move. What's the most money I made in a
month trading?
Uh,
I don't know if I could actually put an
exact number on it, but I'm pretty sure
around $100,000
in a month
and my best month ever around that time.
It's difficult to say because I keep
positions open through months and all
that, but I I know for certain that
going back to March,
I'm up. You know, I made a lot of money
in what was the there was one month
where I was I was making crazy money. I
forget when
we're going back to March. I'm probably
up since then.
That's half a year. I'm up over $200,000
from trading from March,
which is about right.
Um,
max incline, max bidding, max leverage,
max weight on the vest. Yeah, you got to
be careful. You know what I'm saying?
Because
I'm not an elder in a community, by the
way, guys. I'm only 36 years old. You
know what I'm saying? Like, there's
people out here older than me. You know
what I'm saying?
No, but but but I do appreciate that,
man. I It isn't It is crazy to think
that my YouTube channel is going on six
years. That is wild.
That is wild.
How can we possibly go up without
grabbing the liquidity from 60,000?
Bitcoin loves to do that, right? Bitcoin
loves to do that.
So, how much money have I made since
November. Well, I mean, if we're going
to talk about spot trading and leverage
trading, quite a bit. Quite a bit. I
mean, I I I I did very well during this
last
cycle. So, praise the Lord. Praise the
Lord, honestly, cuz
you know, I I had a lot of things going
for me this last cycle.
The 12th is a solar eclipse. Okay,
interesting. Okay, interesting. I've
heard the eclipse line up with the
market tops and bottoms. What's my
prediction for market open tomorrow?
Shout out to Juan Estrada. Look, I
really don't know, guys. I'm going to be
honest with you. I'm just I'm here right
now to be very objective on the chart.
Like
I've given the potential scenarios and
I've given you how I plan to trade each
scenario. So I don't know what's going
to happen. I could see either bullish or
bearish cases happening here. um because
of the tight consolidation because we're
at a key area of resistance having
formed this disgusting looking bearish
ascending channel here which could so
easily come back down to the value area
low of the range. Right? I could see
that scenario playing out perfectly and
I'm looking for a long trade from the
back test of this zone right here.
Right? Absolutely 100% looking for a
long trade from there. I could see this
breaking out to the upside and us coming
to $68,000. And I'm absolutely going to
be looking for a short trade from the
top of this local range. I could see us
flipping this into support based on
these high time frames. And I'd
absolutely be looking for a back test
and a long trade up to here, right? Um
that's how I'm that's how I'm playing
the market right now.
So, and honestly, that's that is the if
you're a trader, that is the way to
trade. All right. People coming in here
making predictions. Honestly,
over time that is not go that is not
going to be profitable,
right? That is not going to be
profitable. The the the market [music]
it can do anything. And so the the best
way in my experience to come in and
consistently [music] grow an account is
to be objective and say anything could
happen and then plan for the different
scenarios. I mean, if [music] you don't
if you don't plan for the scenarios,
then you're going to miss a trade. You
know what I'm saying?
So, what are you going to be the guy
that like on New York Open, we get a big
pump and then you long the top and then
we just happen to get the fake out
like or are you going to be the guy that
longs before New York open? Maybe maybe
you make some money on that. Like, good
for you. Or maybe you short before New
York open, you make some money. Good for
you. But longterm that is not the way to
go. All right. long term, the way to go
was to say, you know what, there's a
really important resistance right here.
There's a really important resistance
right here. There's a really important
support right here. Right now, we're
chopping around.
So,
I mean, you could plan, too. You could
make a plan to say if on New York open
we lose this trend line and bearishly
back test it, that could also give you
the setup there to take a short.
But trying to predict market moves and
going in beforehand, that is that is not
a long-term strategy for success. That
is a long-term strategy to make quick
money sometimes and then get wrecked
often.
But, you know, some people do it that
way and good for you guys. Good for you
guys. Like, if that's how you do it,
excellent. I I
excellent. I I I wish I could be you,
right? I wish I could be the guy [music]
that just, you know, lives a normal life
and goes to his job and comes home and
drinks beer and eats pizza and watches
sports ball and just so happy with life.
All right, but I can't be that guy. I
wish I could be the guy that just comes
to the chart and says, "How am I feeling
today, long or short, and just make
money and being happy, you know? People
do that." All right, good for you guys.
I'm not like that. You know, I wish I
was. I wish I was. you know,
um,
no predictions every day. I have a
method and a market psychology. That's
what's up. That's what's up. You know,
guys, you know what's really sad about
today?
It's really sad about today is I don't
have my [music] I I'm not outside so I
can't pee in the bushes. So, you know
what we're going to do today? We are
going to
going to pee out the window. All right.
We're going to pee out the window there.
Look how crazy that window looks.
Yeah, let's pee out the window.
When did I feel like I was at a point
where there wasn't much left to improve?
Man, there's always room to improve in
trading. When did I feel like I could
actually do this?
Long-term?
Probably around the time of the the
pandemic
is when I felt like I could actually do
this.
Of course, this is after losing like
tens of thousands of dollars.
That's when I actually felt like I could
actually do this. [music]
Man, it feels good to pee. I'll tell you
guys.
Yeah. Honestly, like some people,
they're good at just coming into the
charts and they just make a prediction.
That is not how I roll. Because here's
the problem. I I end up playing reverse
reverse reverse reverse reverse reverse
reverse reverse reverse psychology. Like
man, everyone's so bullish right now,
which is why I should short, but
everyone's
bullish and everyone's thinking that
everyone should short because everyone's
so bullish, which means I should long,
but you know, if I long, then the market
makers know that everyone's thinking
that because everyone's so bullish,
people should short, but then they
should really long. So that means I
should really short. And then like, you
know, I just can't I can't handle that.
You know what I'm saying? Uh, don't lose
your willie.
Um,
yeah, no pee juggling here. Do I trade
stocks? I don't trade stocks. I hold a
lot of stocks. I have a stock portfolio
in life. Boring stocks. Boring stocks
that pay dividends. You know, CocaCola,
uh, [music] that kind of stuff. The
boring stuff.
Um,
rather than get all my money taken by
stop-loss getting hunted, would rather
just dump a large summoned spot. Yeah,
that's that I mean that is that is
really the way to go. All right, let's
check some other assets. I told someone
I was going to check Zcash, then we'll
check Solana.
Let's check out Zcash.
Interesting.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Did we hit the 382?
We front ran the 382. [music]
Let's check out the volume.
since 2021.
Wow.
Wow. I mean, the best long setup on
Zcash right now is obviously going to be
to take out the lows
again and bounce from our 382 and then
come back to the top of this.
Um
but then after that I have to say if
we're going to lose this then the PC
becomes the next place to look and
that's going to be quite a bit lower.
But altcoins love to retrace in between
the 786 and 886. And whenever you have
the 786 886 confluence with a dang
P that's always the place to look.
So again, I'm not saying we're going to
come down here. I'm just ask asking
myself, you know, if I could have any
setup in the world, what would it be?
Well, for me,
this would absolutely be a pretty nice
setup to long the thing. Um,
let's go ahead and pull a Fibonacci as
well from the high to a potential low
down there. [music] Yeah, cuz if we come
down to that area, look, the back test
of the Fibonacci golden pocket will be
at the value area high. So even in an
ultra bearish scenario, we come down, we
can get a bounce and then we reject from
the support resistance flip and come
down lower.
Um but also, you know, just coming down
to here
and losing this level, but then getting
a reclaim of that level, it is a
valid long in my opinion and we could
shoot for the top of the range.
Could be pretty nice. Could be pretty
nice right there. We would have a pretty
nice bullish divergence on the weekly if
that happened. If that happened, [music]
um,
the only other short trade that I could
possibly imagine looking for would be a
fake out of the highs. But I mean, this
is a very bullish trend.
It is a bullish trend.
But yeah, the only other possible short
scenario I would be I could I could
imagine would be coming up to take 750
with some bearish divergences and
getting a fake out. I I really don't
like the way that would look because
this, you could say,
is forming a bullish cup and handle.
And I'm not really the biggest fan of
trading cup and handles myself, but if
you are a fan of trading a cup and
handle,
I mean,
the breakout of $743
could potentially take us to, let's go
ahead and just see where that could
actually take us based on the measured
move.
It's going to take us over $1,000. It's
going to take us like a $1,200 Zcash.
And it's pretty crazy, but that would be
the technical target of the
um [music] cup and handle. Man, it would
be much nicer to come down here and get
that double bottom and then come up to
the top. That would be nice.
You could also, I mean, it depends how
you look at it, but you know, that's why
I said you could look for something like
this and then just come right back into
the middle. You know, if we're going to
do nothing and we just continue to trade
sideways,
you know, these two zones are the place.
[music] Let's take a look at soul.
Hop aboard the soul train. [music]
The soul train. The soul plane. I ain't
playing. I ain't playing y'all.
Oh snap.
Go for the round then.
I like them better to be honest. Don't
you?
Sorry guys. [music]
Good old talk to text over here. Jason
Casper, such a boomer.
I am such a boomer, man. All right. So,
so Lana, what's the deal with this
thing? Well,
the end of August, we potentially
confirm a green dot, a big green dot on
the monthly. That's not a bearish signal
at all. Two week has a confirmed bullish
divergence.
You know, I obviously when it comes to
these assets, I do believe that Bitcoin
is going to determine whether or not the
market gets bullish or bearish.
>> [music]
>> Um,
if we start to change structure and make
a higher high on our two-weekly, then
I'd say there's a really good chance
that we continue up even higher. And so
I would be looking basically for a break
of $100 and then like a back test coming
down between 85 90 and I'd basically be
looking to back test that PC and then
take it up to the uh the value area high
or even our golden pocket, right?
Something like that. Assuming that this
is our [music] range to be trading here.
Um,
let's put it on log scale. [music]
Put it on log scale and zoom.
I mean, the only other, you know, what's
crazy here is like [music] really, I
mean,
if we're going to come lower here, I you
know, I don't even want to say it. I
don't want to say it. You know, people
are going to hate me for saying this,
but if we're going to if we're just
going to look at like major supports
here, like if we come lower than this,
our next major support resistance flip
is going to be this, guys. [music] Like,
you know, taking it back to here.
So, let's go ahead and pull the macro
volume.
Oh, I mean, even the PC is is coming
down. Oh, man. I mean, can you imagine a
$25 Solana?
But yeah, change of structure, I'd say,
you know, fair enough. Fair enough to to
feel bullish. Um, [music]
we have bullish divergences. We have
signals on the monthly that we could
could be bottoming, especially if you
know it's January and Bitcoin [music]
and other assets are in bullish market
structure as well. Um, as far as buying
this thing on spot,
now I got to be honest with you guys,
like
I bought a lot of Solana on spot in
November of 2022, December of 2022.
[music] I haven't bought anymore and I
also haven't sold any.
I thought about selling a little bit at
the all-time high. I did not. All right.
It's a very sad story. our altcoin
account that we have on spot here in the
Casper household because
I just tell you that it was looking
pretty good for a while there.
It was looking pretty pretzly, you know,
but then things turned upside down real
quick. But it was looking good like
gluten glyphosate covered genetically
modified wheat was looking really good.
But then things took a turn for the
worst.
But I'm not buying any Solana on spot
here. If we're going to look at how far
we've come from the all-time high,
80%, that's a pretty significant
discount. That's a pretty significant
discount, honestly. And if we go from
the bare market bottom, we're still up
right now 900% from the bare market
bottom. So, from the time that I bought
Soul Oh, I'm sorry. This is No, this
Yeah, from Yeah, that's that's it. Yeah.
November 2022. I'm still up pretty good
on I'm still up pretty good on my spot.
Soul. I have no reason to buy here. Um,
if you do want to open up, build a
position, there's potentially another
70% area that we could come to. Now, it
doesn't mean we're going to come to
there.
Um,
but objectively speaking, I'd say a 75%
discount, that's a good place to start
DCAing in. And if the bottom is in and
we get surprised and especially if we
have an altcoin bull market this time
around, which we very well may just to
catch everyone off guard,
you know, Solana is a decent asset.
It's a decent asset.
Why are people becoming so boring when
you see a thousand likes in the first
half hour? It is because, my friend,
crypto is dead. All right? The crypto
space is dead. Trading is dead. There's
no hype. All our dreams, all our hopes
and dreams have been smashed to
smitherines, bro. All our hopes and
dreams have been smashed to
smitherreens,
right? We were hoping for alt season. We
were hoping for [music] Lambos and,
you know, we were we were hoping for the
hype when and the retail FOMO at the
top. We were hoping for the ETS to shoot
us up to $200,000 Bitcoin, $10,000 ETH,
you know,
$5 Cardono, and then on October 10th,
everyone got liquidated on 2x leverage,
and now nobody cares anymore, right?
It's like the boy who cried wolf, right?
It's it's actually it's our fault. It's
us YouTubers faults, right? Because we
need the thumbnails, we need the
clickbait, we need the hype. So people
are sick of hearing, you know, oh, the
big next move coming. Oh, this, oh,
that. Everyone's already had their hopes
and dreams dashed to smitherreens too
many times and nobody's really trading
in general. Like you go, you search like
analytics for people even just searching
trading in general, not just crypto, but
anything like forex, stocks, it's down,
man. It's down big time. COVID, uh, a
lot of people got into trading during
CO. People were just home. They were
getting free money from the government.
Everyone was into trading then. Now
[music]
no one's really into it anymore,
you know. So,
shout out to Felix. Sweating here in the
south of France. 32° at 9:00 p.m. That's
crazy, man. Assuming that that's not
Fahrenheit.
Do I think trading is dead?
No, I don't think trading is dead. I
mean, trading is something I love to do
and I'm always going to do, but in
general, like,
no, nothing's really dead, guys.
Nothing's really dead. It's just the the
the hype that existed in the crypto
space and the trading space is no longer
there right now. Will it come back?
Yeah, it es and flows. It es and flows.
But you know what? The hype goes along
with the Bitcoin price. So, the hype in
20,
you know, 2020, 2021
was insane. And then the hype in
I think around 2024, like right after
Donald Trump won the election, that that
was the the peak of the hype in crypto.
And then when Trump rug pulled everybody
with his with his altcoin,
um that disenfranchised a lot of people.
Um but man,
I don't think the crypto space will ever
be what it was
anymore. It's going to be more of just
like a traditional market that people
trade, which is sad. I missed the old
days, you know. But hey, you know, it is
what it is.
It is what it is. Shout out to the Gamer
X. Yeah, it's not that. Yeah, trading is
never dead. Um,
so we need a new COVID or a super co.
Well, I Yeah, I I don't know. Like I
don't know. I I don't know if we had
another another shutdown like that. I
don't think it would have the same
effect. You know, the effect of the
first shutdown is still happening. Like
that really like wrecked people in
general. So,
but we'll see. You know, volatility
volatility is a uh a trader's best
friend, right? So if big things happen
in the world
then um
the markets will move. The markets will
move and movement gives you opportunity
in general you know.
Yeah.
Lower time frame analysis of Bitcoin.
Well, in general, I think that if we
break down from this, we're probably
going to head down towards 60K,
right?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
But you know what, guys? It's been a
good stream. I think I am going to head
out, y'all. I think I am going to head
out. [music]
Um, happy Sunday.
Tomorrow morning, Casper Crew VIP live
stream. Last VIP live stream we did for
New York Open, we longed this level
right here on the back test. [music]
So hopefully we'll get another trade
tomorrow morning.
[music] Um, yeah. Hope you guys have a
great evening and I'll see you later.
Peace.